iluvcinema.in 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy

Iluvcinema.in is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to its website.

**Personal Information**

Iluvcinema.in will not collect or save any personal information. Iluvcinema.in will not use forms and all emails that are completely deleted once they have been handled.

We do not place cookies on the computers of visitors to our website.

We do not reveal any personal information to any third party for any reason.

We will never maintain any database storing any personal information about our visitors.

As we do not keep any personal information about our visitors, we do not send you any advertisements or unsolicited information regarding this site.

**Aggregate Information**

Iluvcinema.in uses a web statistics program to track aggregate usage of this site. This program is helped to improve and enlarge the site. It does not allow us to personally identify individual users to the site.

Iluvicnema.in does not give any aggregate information to third parties concerning visitors to this site **.**

**Advertising**

Iluvcinema.in uses a few third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
